A Guide to the Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, RG 1.32 (A2006) FA483
Rockefeller Archive Center
Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, RG 1.32 (A2006)
1982-2005 (Bulk: 1999-2005)
1999-2005
Rockefeller Archive Center
Rockefeller Foundation
FA483
74.67 Cubic Feet 57 standard record storage boxes.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Project files transferred to the RAC by Rockefeller Foundation, 2006.
Arrangement
Reccords are primarily arranged by Program.
Some subgroups may contain portions of the material that are arranged by the Rockefeller Foundation traditional series (country code) and subseries (program letter) structure.
Records are arranged as received. Within folders, materials are primarily arranged in reverse chronological order.
Biographical / Historical
Rockefeller Foundation
The Rockefeller Foundation was established by act of the New York State Legislature approved by the Governor on May 14, 1913, "to promote the well-being of mankind throughout the world." Between 1913 and 1928 the China Medical Board, the International Health Board, and the Division of Medical Education functioned as divisions of the Foundation, concentrating on the administration of programs in public health and medical education. A Division of Studies was created in 1923 to handle projects outside the medical field. These early years were experimental as the new foundation studied the methods of philanthropy and explored its relationships with other Rockefeller boards. Although the Rockefeller Foundation is the largest and best known philanthropy founded by the Rockefeller family, it was neither the first nor the last to be established. The Rockefeller Institute for Medical Research (1901), the General Education Board (1902), the Rockefeller Sanitary Commission for the Eradication of Hookworm Disease (1909), and the Bureau of Social Hygiene (1911) all existed earlier. When the Foundation was created, the Sanitary Commission was disbanded. After the establishment of the Foundation, the Laura Spelman Rockefeller Memorial (1918) and the International Education Board (1923) were created.
The Rockefeller boards and their programs were reconsidered and reorganized in 1927-1928 in order to avoid overlapping programs. The International Health Board of the Foundation was disbanded and an International Health Division was organized. The China Medical Board, Inc., was established as a separately incorporated institution, and the China Medical Board of the Foundation ceased to exist. The Division of Studies was dropped and the Division of Medical Education was phased out. The Laura Spelman Rockefeller Memorial was combined with the Foundation and the Spelman Fund of New York was chartered to continue activities of the LSRM that were not absorbed by the Foundation. The International Education Board was disbanded.
As a result of this reorganization, the Foundation adopted a program which included public health work (administered by the IHD), the advancement of knowledge in the medical and natural sciences (in part taken over from the IEB), the social sciences (formerly the field of the LSRM), and the humanities and arts (shared with the GEB). The Rockefeller Institute and the Bureau of Social Hygiene were not affected by the reorganization. The program adopted by the Foundation at this time remained basically the same for the next twenty years.
Conditions Governing Access
Records more than 10 years old are open for research with select materials restricted as noted. Brittle or damaged items are available at the discretion of RAC. Researchers interested in accessing digital media (floppy disks, CDs, DVDs, etc.) in this collection must use an access surrogate. The original items may not be accessed because of preservation concerns. To request an access surrogate be made, or if you are unsure if there is an access surrogate, please contact an archivist.
Scope and Contents
Grant administration files and related material.
- AC.2006.002: Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, 1994-2004; AC.2006.002; 2.63 Cubic Feet 2 standard record storage boxes, Boxes R3769-R3770; 2 standard record storage boxes, Boxes R3769-R3770.
  - Creativity and Culture (CC), AC.2006.002.1; 2.63 Cubic Feet 2 record storage boxes
    - 2000 CC 003 - SCHOOL OF PLASTIC ARTS (PUERTO RICO) - "PEPON OSORIO IN PUERTO RICO PROJECT", 1999-2003 (Box R3769)
    - 2000 CC 004 - CORNELL UNIVERSITY - EXHIBITION, "BLACKNESS IN COLOR...", 1999-2001 (Box R3769)
    - 2000 CC 005 - MUSEUM OF CONTEMPORARY ART, SAN DIEGO - EXHIBITION, "ULTRA-BAROQUE: ASPECTS OF POST-LATIN AMERICAN ART", 1998-2002 (Box R3769)
    - 2000 CC 006 - UNIVERSITY OF CALIFORNIA (SANTA BARBARA) - EXHIBITION, "JUST ANOTHER POSTER? CHICANO GRAPHIC ARTS IN CALIFORNIA", 1998-2001 (Box R3769)
    - 2000 CC 007 - WORCESTER ART MUSEUM - EXHIBITION, "ANTIOCH: THE LOST ANCIENT CITY", 1999-2001 (Box R3769)
    - 2000 CC 008 - CONSERVANCY FOR TIBETAN ART AND CULTURE - TIBETAN-AMERICAN PARTICIPATION AT SMITHSONIAN FOLKLIFE FESTIVAL, 1999-2001 (Box R3769)
    - 2000 CC 009 - ASIA SOCIETY - CHORUS REPERTORY THEATER PERFORMANCE OF "UTTAR-PRIYADARSHI", 1999-2001 (Box R3769)
    - 2000 CC 011 - SANTA MONICA MUSEUM OF ART - EXHIBITION, "EAST OF THE RIVER: CHICANO ART COLLECTORS ANONYMOUS", 1999-2002 (Box R3769)
    - 2000 CC 012 - FUNDACION ARS/TEOR/ETICA (COSTA RICA) - REGIONAL SYMPOSIUM ON CONTEMPORARY ARTISTIC PRACTICES IN CENTRAL AMERICA), 1999-2003 (Box R3769)
    - 2000 CC 015 - MONGOL-AMERICAN CULTURAL ASSOCIATION - FESTIVAL OF MONGOLIA 2000, 1999-2001 (Box R3769)
    - 2000 CC 016 - PANTOJA, ANTONIA - LIFE AND WORK OF PANTOJA IN PUERTO RICAN COMMUNITY, 1998-2001 (Box R3769)
    - 2000 CC 017 - RHIZOME COMMUNICATIONS - RHIZOME ARTBASE, 1999-2001 (Box R3769)
    - 2000 CC 019 - ALASKA NATIVE HERITAGE CENTER - "KAYAK SUMMER", 1998-2001 (Box R3769)
    - 2000 CC 021 - LINCOLN CENTER FOR THE PERFORMING ARTS - FESTIVAL 2000, 2000-2001 (Box R3769)
    - 2000 CC 022 - IDRIS ACKAMOOR AND CULTURAL ODYSSEY - 2001 PERFORMANCE FESTIVAL, 2000-2002 (Box R3769)
    - 2000 CC 025 - BANG ON A CAN - MARATHON 2000, 2000-2001 (Box R3769)
    - 2000 CC 029 - BARD COLLEGE - EXHIBITION OF WORKS OF ISAAC JULIEN, 2000-2001 (Box R3769)
    - 2000 CC 030 - MEXICO-NORTH RESEARCH NETWORK - SIERRA TARAHUMARA DIVERSITY PROJECT, 2000-2001 (Box R3770)
    - 2000 CC 031 - UNIVERSITY OF MASSACHUSETTS (AMHERST) - NEW WORLD THEATER'S "INTERSECTION II", 2000-2002 (Box R3770)
    - 2000 CC 037 - MATTRESS FACTORY - EXHIBITION, "VISUAL SOUND", 2000-2005 (Box R3770)
    - 2000 CC 038 - MUSEUM ASSOCIATES - EXHIBITION, "THE ROAD TO AZTLAN ...", 1996-2002 (Box R3770)
    - 2000 CC 042 - AMERICAN REPERTORY THEATRE - "DRAWN TO DEATH: A THREE PANEL OPERA", 2000-2005 (Box R3770)
    - 2000 CC 043 - ARTS FOR ST. ANN'S - "SONG CYCLE FOR PUPPETS", 2000-2002 (Box R3770)
    - 2000 CC 044 - ASIA SOCIETY - "FLOATING BOX: A STORY IN CHINATOWN", 2000-2005 (Box R3770)
    - 2000 CC 045 - BATES COLLEGE - "THE CARAVAN PROJECT", 2000-2001 (Box R3770)
    - 2000 CC 046 - BORDERLANDS THEATER - "ELECTRICIDAD", 2000-2002 (Box R3770)
    - 2000 CC 047 - CHILDREN'S THEATRE CO. - MULTI-MEDIA WORK, "THE BEGGARS STRIKE", 2000-2003 (Box R3770)
    - 2000 CC 048 - CORNERSTONE THEATER CO. - "CITY-WIDE BRIDGE" PROJECT, 2000-2001 (Box R3770)
    - 2000 CC 049 - DANSPACE PROJECT - "/ASUNDER", 2000-2003 (Box R3770)
    - 2000 CC 050 - ELEVATOR REPAIR SERVICE - THEATER WORK, "EXPERTS", 2000-2002 (Box R3770)
    - 2000 CC 051 - FRONTERA@HYDE PARK THEATRE - THEATER WORK, "CON FLAMA" (Box R3770)
    - 2000 CC 052 - GAMELAN SEKAR JAYA - BALINESE DANCE DRAMA WITH PUPPETRY, 2000-2001 (Box R3770)
    - 2000 CC 053 - COATES PERFORMANCE WORKS - LIVE AND ONLINE PERFORMANCE PIECE, "BETTER BAD NEWS", 2000-2004 (Box R3770)
    - 2000 CC 054 - GREAT SMALL WORKS - "THE SATIE CABARET PROJECT", 2000-2002 (Box R3770)
    - 2000 CC 055 - HIGHER GROUNDS PROJECTS - PARTICIPATORY DANCE/PARTY CONCERT, 2000-2002 (Box R3770)
    - 2000 CC 057 - INTERSECTION FOR THE ARTS - "MISSION INDIANS", 2000-2002 (Box R3770)
    - 2000 CC 058 - JAZZ INSTITUTE OF CHICAGO - MUSIC WORK, "CONJECTURES", 2000-2003 (Box R3770)
    - 2000 CC 059 - JUMP START PERFORMANCE CO. - "TO MY CHAGRIN", 2000-2002 (Box R3770)
    - 2000 CC 060 - KITCHEN (THE) - MULTI-MEDIA PERFORMANCE, "CONFERENCE OF THE BIRDS", 2000-2002 (Box R3770)
    - 2000 CC 061 - KITKA WOMEN'S VOCAL ENSEMBLE - "THE NEW FOLKSONGS COMISSIONING PROJECT", 2000-2004 (Box R3770)
    - 2000 CC 062 - KRONOS QUARTET - "AEGEAN CROSSINGS", 2000-2001 (Box R3770)
    - 2000 CC 064 - MA-YI THEATRE ENSEMBLE - "MIDDLE FINGER", 2000-2001 (Box R3770)
- AC.2006.004: Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, 1996-2004; AC.2006.004; 2.63 Cubic Feet 2 standard record storage boxes, Boxes R3771-R3772; 2 standard record storage boxes, Boxes R3771-R3772.
  - Creativity and Culture (CC), AC.2006.004.1; 2.63 Cubic Feet 2 record storage boxes
    - 2000 CC 065 - MONTCLAIR STATE UNIVERSITY - "MOTHER COURAGE AND HER CHILDREN", 2000-2002 (Box R3771)
    - 2000 CC 066 - MUSEUM OF CONTEMPORARY ART - SOLO PERFORMANCE WORK, "ICELAND", 2000-2002 (Box R3771)
    - 2000 CC 067 - MUSIC-THEATRE GROUP - CHAMBER OPERA, "FANGS", 2000-2004 (Box R3771)
    - 2000 CC 070 - PAINTED BRIDE ART CENTER - MULTl-MEDIA PERFORMANCE WORK, "DOGON PM", 2000-2003 (Box R3771)
    - 2000 CC 072 - PERFORMANCE SPACE 122 - NAVIGATIONAL DANCE PROJECT, 2000-2001 (Box R3771)
    - 2000 CC 073 - PUBLIC THEATER - "BOOK OF THE DEAD (SECOND AVE)", 2000-2001 (Box R3771)
    - 2000 CC 074 - STREB/RINGSIDE - MULTl-DISCIPLINARY WORK, "ACTION HEROES", 2000-2003 (Box R3771)
    - 2000 CC 075 - SEATTLE CHILDREN'S THEATRE - "MASK OF THE UNICORN WARRIOR", 2000-2001 (Box R3771)
    - 2000 CC 076 - SPIDERWOMAN THEATER - "PERSISTENCE OF MEMORY", 2000-2004 (Box R3771)
    - 2000 CC 077 - PETRONIO DANCE CO. - "STRANGE ATTRACTORS PART II", 2000-2004 (Box R3771)
    - 2000 CC 078 - SYMPHONY SPACE - MULTl-MEDIA DANCE WORK, 2000-2002 (Box R3771)
    - 2000 CC 079 - BROWN DANCE CO. - DANCE OPERA, "LUCI MIE TRADITRICI", 2000-2002 (Box R3771)
    - 2000 CC 081 - WORKING THEATRE CO. - "ABUNDANCE", 2000-2003 (Box R3771)
    - 2000 CC 082 - WORLD MUSIC INSTITUTE - "FROM RAJASTHAN TO ANDALUSIA", 2000-2002 (Box R3771)
    - 2000 CC 083 - YERBA BUENA CENTER FOR THE ARTS - WORKS FOR CELLO, 2000-2001 (Box R3771)
    - 2000 CC 084 - ZACCHO S.F. - SITE-SPECIFIC WORK, "PICTURE BAYVIEW", 2000-2002 (Box R3771)
    - 2000 CC 086 - INSTITUTE FOR ADVANCED STUDY - NEW MEDIA AND INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY STUDY, 2000-2001 (Box R3771)
    - 2000 CC 089 - ALFRED UNIVERSITY - "EXPERIMENTS IN SCIENCE-TECHNOLOGY-ART RESIDENCIES, 2000-2002 (Box R3771)
    - 2000 CC 095 - ROCKEFELLER FOUNDATION - GRANTMAKERS IN FILM, TELEVISION, AND VIDEO, 1996-2000 (Box R3771)
    - 2000 CC 097 - DANCE THEATER WORKSHOP - SUITCASE FUND FOR MEKONG DELTA IN SOUTHEAST ASIA, 1999-2003 (Box R3771)
    - 2000 CC 098 - WOMEN'S WORLD ORGANIZATION FOR RIGHTS, LITERATURE AND DEVELOPMENT - ORGANIZATIONAL STRATEGY AND PLAN, 2000-2001 (Box R3771)
    - 2000 CC 100 - INTERNATIONAL FILM SEMINARS, INC. - DIGITAL FLAHERTY SEMINAR, 2000-2002 (Box R3772)
    - 2000 CC 101 - SMITHSONIAN INSTITUTION - "A MORE PERFECT UNION" ONLINE, 1999-2002 (Box R3772)
    - 2000 CC 103 - JEWISH MUSEUM - "MOROCCO: JEWS AND ART IN A MUSLIM WORLD", 2000-2004 (Box R3772)
    - 2000 CC 104 - NATIONAL ASSOCIATION OF LATINO ARTS AND CULTURE -THIRD NATIONAL CONFERENCE, 2000-2002 (Box R3772)
    - 2000 CC 106 - AID TO ARTISANS - "CRAFTS IN THE LAND OF RICE CULTURE", 2000-2001 (Box R3772)
    - 2000 CC 109 - INDEPENDENT CURATORS INTERNATIONAL - EXHIBITION, "TELEMATIC CONNECTIONS: THE VIRTUAL EMBRACE", 2000-2001 (Box R3772)
    - 2000 CC 110 - ART & SCIENCE COLLABORATIONS, INC. - ARTSCI2001 SYMPOSIUM AND THINK TANKS, 2000-2001 (Box R3772)
    - 2000 CC 111 - NEW YORK UNIVERSITY - "TACTILE MEDIA" ORGANIZING CONFERENCE, 2000-2002 (Box R3772)
    - 2000 CC 113 - CANADA COUNCIL FOR THE ARTS - WORLD SUMMIT ON THE ARTS AND CULTURE, 2000-2001 (Box R3772)
    - 2000 CC 115 - ACADEMIA EUROPAEA (ENGLAND) - COLLABORATION AND OWNERSHIP IN THE DIGITAL ECONOMY (CODE) CONFERENCE, 2000-2002 (Box R3772)
    - 2000 CC 119 - UNIVERSITY OF PARIS 1 (FRANCE) - NAM JUNE PAIK DVD-ROM, 2000-2004 (Box R3772)
    - 2000 CC 121 - NEW YORK FOUNDATION FOR THE ABTS - CULTURAL PLAN FOR NEW YORK CITY, 2000-2002 (Box R3772)
    - 2000 CC 122 - NEW YORK FOUNDATION FOR THE ARTS - NEA'S "AMBASSADORS FOR THE ARTS REUNION", 2000-2001 (Box R3772)
    - 2000 CC 124 - CORNELL UNIVERSITY - EXHIBITION, "COMING UP ON THE SEASON: MIGRANT FARM WORKERS IN THE NORTHEAST", 2000-2002 (Box R3772)
- AC.2006.013: Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, 1997-2004; AC.2006.013; 2.63 Cubic Feet 2 standard record storage boxes, Boxes R3773-R3774; 2 standard record storage boxes, Boxes R3773-R3774.
  - Creativity and Culture (CC), AC.2006.013.1; 2.63 Cubic Feet 2 record storage boxes
    - 2000 CC 126 - MEXICAN FINE ARTS CENTER MUSEUM - EXHIBITION, "MEXICANIDAD", 1999-2004 (Box R3773)
    - 2000 CC 127 - SEATTLE ART MUSEUM - EXHIBITION, "TREASURES OF A LOST CIVILIZATION: ANCIENT CHINESE ART FROM SICHUAN", 1999-2002 (Box R3773)
    - 2000 CC 129 - CYBER-SITE NEW MEDIA RESEARCH CENTER, INC. - NEW MEDIA INFORMATION GATEWAY DATABASE, 2000-2003 (Box R3773)
    - 2000 CC 130 - NEW YORK FOUNDATION FOR THE ARTS - "CROSSOVER", WEB LAB'S NEW MEDIA WORKSHOP, 2000-2002 (Box R3773)
    - 2000 CC 135 - EARTHWAYS FOUNDATION - "WORLD FESTIVAL OF SACRED MUSIC, THE AMERICAS", 1998-2002 (Box R3773)
    - 2000 CC 136 - UNIVERSITY OF SOUTHERN CALIFORNIA - "LABRYNTH: LEVEL FOUR", 2000-2002 (Box R3773)
    - 2000 CC 137 - CITY COLLEGE, CITY UNIVERSITY OF NEW YORK (DOMINICAN STUDIES INSTITUTE) - CONFERENCES ON DIVERSITY AND DEMOCRACY, 2000-2004 (Box R3773)
    - 2000 CC 143 - APPALSHOP - CENTRAL APPALACHIAN FESTIVAL/ARTIST AND COMMUNITY GATHERING, 2000-2004 (Box R3773)
      - Journeys Home, 2006.013.001; 1 Item(s) compact disc
    - 2000 CC 144 - DOWNTOWN COMMUNITY TELEVISION CENTER, INC. - "CYBERSTUDIO FOR THE ARTS", 2000-2004 (Box R3773)
    - 2000 CC 146 - COLUMBIA COLLEGE (CHICAGO) - STUDY OF INFORMAL ARTS IN AMERICA, 2000-2002 (Box R3773)
    - 2000 CC 148 - CARNEGIE INSTITUTE - 'POPULAR CULTURES...", 2000-2002 (Box R3773)
    - 2000 CC 150 - COUNCIL ON FOREIGN RELATIONS - PROJECT ON ETHNIC CONFLICT, PARTITION AND RECONSTRUCTION, 1998-2005 (Box R3774)
    - 2000 CC 153 - ROBERT ABBE MUSEUM OF STONE AGE ANTIQUITIES - EXHIBITION, "THE FOUR MOLLYS: WOMEN OF THE DAWN", 2000-2004 (Box R3774)
  - Communication for Social Change (CS), AC.2006.013.2; 1.31 Cubic Feet 1 record storage box
    - 2000 CS 005 - NATIONAL PUBLIC RADIO - COVERAGE OF RACE AND ETHNICITY, 1997-2001 (Box R3774)
    - 2000 CS 006 - (COMMUNICATION FOR SOCIAL CHANGE) - BC CONFERENCE: REALITIES AND NEW APROACHES: DEVELOPMENT COMMUNICATIONS IN THE 21ST CENTURY, 1999-2001 (Box R3774)
  - Food Security (FS), AC.2006.013.3; 1.31 Cubic Feet 1 record storage box
    - 2000 FS 011 - UNIVERSITY OF HYDERABAD (INDIA) - BIOTECHNOLOGY CAREER FELLOWSHIP FOR ARJULA R. REDDY, 1999-2002 (Box R3774)
    - 2000 FS 014 - OBAFEMI AWOLOWO UNIVERSITY (NIGERIA) - ESSENTIAL ELECTRONIC AGRICULTURAL LIBRARY (TEEAL), 1999-2002 (Box R3774)
    - 2000 FS 015 - AFRICA UNIVERSITY (ZIMBABWE) - ESSENTIAL ELECTRONIC AGRICULTURAL LIBRARY (TEEAL), 1999-2002 (Box R3774)
    - 2000 FS 019 - TROPICAL SOIL BIOLOGY AND FERTILITY PROGRAMME (TSBF) - NETWORKING AND RESEARCH ACTIVITIES IN AFRICA, 1988-2002; 3 folders. (Box R3774)
- AC.2006.019: Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, 1998-2005; AC.2006.019; 1.31 Cubic Feet 1 standard record storage box, Box R3776; 1 standard record storage box, Box R3776.
  - Food Security (FS), AC.2006.019.1; 1.31 Cubic Feet 1 record storage box
    - 2000 FS 092 - MALAWI - AGRICULTURAL SECTOR STUDY, 1998-2002 (Box R3776)
    - 2000 FS 092 - MALAWI - AGRICULTURAL SECTOR STUDY - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL, 1998-2002 (Box R3776)
    - 2000 FS 103 - NATIONAL AGRICULTURAL RESEARCH ORGANISATION (UGANDA) - BANANA CROPPING SYSTEMS PROJECT, 1998-2002 (Box R3776)
    - 2000 FS 107 - TROPICAL SOIL BIOLOGY AND FERTILITY PROGRAMME (KENYA) - ALL AFRICAN BIOLOGICAL NITROGEN FIXATION CONGRESS, 1999-2001 (Box R3776)
    - 2000 FS 120 - KENYA AGRICULTURAL RESEARCH INSTITUTE - 18TH CONFERENCE OF SOIL SCIENCE SOCIETY OF EAST AFRICA, 2000-2002 (Box R3776)
    - 2000 FS 124 - INTERNATIONAL MAIZE AND WHEAT IMPROVEMENT CENTER (MEXICO) - GREEN MANURE COVER CROPS SYSTEMS DATABASE, 2000-2002 (Box R3776)
    - 2000 FS 127 - INTERNATIONAL INSTITUTE OF RURAL RECONSTRUCTION (PHILIPPINES) - CONFERENCE ON TECHNOLOGY DEVELOPMENT, 2000-2003 (Box R3776)
    - 2000 FS 129 - ROTHAMSTED EXPERIMENTAL STATION (ENGLAND) - STRIGA HERMONTHICA SUPPRESSION IN A MAIZE/DESMODIUM INTERCROP SYSTEM, 1999-2002 (Box R3776)
    - 2000 FS 152 - OKOGBENIN, EMMANUEL - GENETIC MAPPING OF CASSAVA, 1998-2003 (Box R3776)
    - 2000 FS 157 - TROPICAL SOIL BIOLOGY AND FERTILITY PROGRAMME (KENYA) - ORGANIC MATTER MANAGEMENT IN MALAWI AND ZIMBABWE, 1998-2002 (Box R3776)
    - 2000 FS 160 - AFRICAN CROP SCIENCE SOCIETY (SOUTH AFRICA) - FIFTH ALL AFRICA SCIENCE CONGRESS, 2000-2002 (Box R3776)
    - 2000 FS 169 - UNIVERSITY OF OTTAWA (CANADA) - RESEARCH AND BIOSAFETY ASSESSMENT OF TRANSGENIC CROPS FOR INSECT RESISTANCE, 2000-2005 (Box R3776)
    - 2000 FS 170 - DONALD DANFORTH PLANT SCIENCE CENTER - SYMPOSIUM ON SALT AND DROUGHT TOLERANCE, 2000-2002 (Box R3776)
    - 2000 FS 175 - JOHN INNES CENTRE (ENGLAND) - GLOBAL AGRICULTURE CONFERENCE, 2000-2003 (Box R3776)
    - 2000 FS 176 - PHILIPPINE RICE RESEARCH INSTITUTE - ASIAN AGRICULTURE CONGRESS 2001, 2000-2002 (Box R3776)
    - 2000 FS 178 - (FOOD SECURITY) - SECOND INTERNATIONAL APOMIXIS CONFERENCE, 2000-2002 (Box R3776)
- AC.2006.023: Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, 1993-2004; AC.2006.023; 2.63 Cubic Feet 2 standard record storage boxes, Boxes R3777-R3778.; 2 standard record storage boxes, Boxes R3777-R3778.
  - Food Security (FS), AC.2006.023.1; 1.31 Cubic Feet 1 record storage box
    - 2000 FS 179 - WEST AFRICA RICE DEVELOPMENT ASSOCIATION (IVORY COAST) - WORKSHOP ON SUSTAINABLE RICE DEVELOPMENT, 2000-2004 (Box R3777)
    - 2000 FS 180 - ZIMBABWE - LANDS AND AGRICULTURE (MINISTRY OF) - INTEGRATED NUTRIENT MANAGEMENT PLANNING, 2000-2002 (Box R3777)
    - 2000 FS 182 - ZIMBABWE - LANDS, AGRICULTURE AND RURAL DEVELOPMENT (MINISTRY OF) - SOIL FERTILITY RESEARCH, 1996-2003 (Box R3777)
    - 2000 FS 183 - LOWLANDS AGRICULTURAL & TECHNICAL SERVICES LIMITED (KENYA) - TRAVEL COSTS FOR MOSES ONIM TO VISIT MAHYCO, 2000-2003 (Box R3777)
    - 2000 FS 185 - TROPICAL SOIL BIOLOGY AND FERTILITY PROGRAM (KENYA) - WEBPAGE AND PROCEEDINGS OF FORMAT SYMPOSIUM, 2000-2002 (Box R3777)
    - 2000 FS 186 - INTERNATIONAL CENTRE FOR GENETIC ENGINEERING AND BIOTECHNOLOGY (INDIA) - MARKER-ASSISTED SELECTION OF GALL MIDGE RESISTANCE IN CULTIVATED RICE, 1998-2001 (Box R3777)
    - 2000 FS 187 - (FOOD SECURITY) - BC TEAM: SOIL FERTILITY IN AFRICA, 2001 (Box R3777)
  - Global Inclusion (GI), AC.2006.023.2; 2.63 Cubic Feet 2 record storage boxes
    - 2000 GI 004 - HARVARD UNIVERSITY - RE- SURVEY IN NORTH BIHAR, INDIA, 1999-2002 (Box R3777)
    - 2000 GI 014 - TIDES CENTER - LABOR RIGHTS IN GLOBAL ECONOMY, 1999-2002 (Box R3777)
    - 2000 GI 016 - INTERNATIONAL SERVICE FOR THE ACQUISITION OF AGRl-BIOTECH APPLICATIONS - SOUTHEAST ASIA KNOWLEDGE CENTER, 1999-2001 (Box R3777)
    - 2000 GI 020 - INTERNATIONAL PLANNED PARENTHOOD FEDERATION (ENGLAND) - EDUCATIONAL INITIATIVE IN DENMARK AND FINLAND, 1993-2002; 4 folders. (Box R3778)
    - 2000 GI 020 - INTERNATIONAL PLANNED PARENTHOOD FEDERATION (ENGLAND) - EDUCATIONAL INITIATIVE IN DENMARK AND FINLAND - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL, 1993-2002; 2 folders. (Box R3778)
    - 2000 GI 022 - INSTITUTE FOR AGRICULTURE AND TRADE POLICY - BC CONFERENCE: BUILDING A PEOPLES' MOVEMENT OF GLOBAL DEMOCRACY (Box R3778)
    - 2000 GI 024 - HUMAN RIGHTS WATCH - PEACE AND CONFLICT RESEARCH PAPER, 2000-2001 (Box R3778)
    - 2000 GI 025 - INTERNATIONAL INSTITUTE OF STRATEGIC STUDIES - ADMINISTRATION OF WAR TORN SOCIETIES, 2000-2001 (Box R3778)
    - 2000 GI 026 - UNIVERSITY OF MASSACHUSETTS - TRAINING PROGRAM IN CLEAN PRODUCTION, 2000-2001 (Box R3778)
    - 2000 GI 030 - UNIVERSITY OF PENNSYLVANIA - INTERNTIONAL DATABASE ON IPR, 2000-2003 (Box R3778)
- AC.2006.029: Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, 1994-2005; AC.2006.029; 3.94 Cubic Feet 3 standard record storage boxes, Boxes R3779-R3781.; 3 standard record storage boxes, Boxes R3779-R3781.
  - Global Inclusion (GI), AC.2006.029.1; 3.94 Cubic Feet 3 record storage boxes
    - 2000 GI 040 - AFRICABIO (SOUTH AFRICA) - WORKSHOP ON FOOD AND AGRICULTURAL BIOTECHNOLOGY, 2000-2002 (Box R3779)
    - 2000 GI 041 - WORLD MEDIA FOUNDATION - RADIO JOURNAL ON GENETICALLY MODIFIED AGRICULTURE, "LIVING ON EARTH", 2000-2001 (Box R3779)
    - 2000 GI 042 - NEW SCHOOL UNIVERSITY - " WORLD POLICY JOURNAL", 2000-2003 (Box R3779)
    - 2000 GI 043 - INTERNATIONAL COUNCIL ON HUMAN RIGHTS POLICY (SWITZERLAND) - ACCOUNTABILITY OF ARMED GROUPS, 2000-2001 (Box R3779)
    - 2000 GI 044 - CIRCLE FOUNDATION - "VOX POPULI" PROJECT, 2000-2001 (Box R3779)
    - 2000 GI 049 - ECONOMIC AFFAIRS BUREAU - CORPORATE DOMINANCE AND CONFLICTS, 2000-2003 (Box R3779)
    - 2000 GI 054 - INTERNATIONAL CENTER FOR NOT-FOR-PROFIT LAW - SUB-SAHARAN AFRICA COMPONENT OF A DATA BASE PROJECT, 2000-2004 (Box R3779)
    - 2000 GI 055 - CONSUMER FEDERATION OF AMERICA FOUNDATION - AGRICULTURAL BIOTECHNOLOGY ISSUES, 2000-2001 (Box R3779)
    - 2000 GI 061 - BREAD FOR THE WORLD INSTITUTE - BIOTECHNOLOGY AND CAMPAIGN TO REDUCE HUNGER IN AFRICA, 2000-2001 (Box R3779)
    - 2000 GI 062 - MONTREAL INTERNATIONAL FORUM (CANADA) - HUMAN SECURITY AND GLOBAL GOVERNANCE, 2000-2004 (Box R3779)
    - 2000 GI 063 - WORLD RESOURCES INSTITUTE - WATER MANAGEMENT ISSUES IN MEKONG REGION, 2000-2002 (Box R3779)
    - 2000 GI 064 - PACIFIC INSTITUTE FOR STUDIES IN DEVELOPMENT, ENVIRONMENT, AND SECURITY - WORLD'S WATER, BOOK, 2000-2003 (Box R3779)
    - 2000 GI 065 - PACIFIC INSTITUTE FOR STUDIES IN DEVELOPMENT, ENVIRONMENT, AND SECURITY - WATER RESOURCES AND GLOBALIZATION AND PRIVATIZATION, 2000-2003 (Box R3779)
    - 2000 GI 068 - DEVELOPMENT GROUP FOR ALTERNATIVE POLICIES - ALLIANCE FOR RESPONSIBLE TRADE'S PROGRAM IN THE AMERICAS, 2000-2001 (Box R3779)
    - 2000 GI 069 - HANOI AGRICULTURAL UNIVERSITY (VIETNAM) - WORKSHOP ON WATER AND LAND USE, 2000-2001 (Box R3779)
    - 2000 GI 070 - WORLD RESOURCES INSTITUTE - MILLENNIUM ECOSYSTEM ASSESSMENT, 2000-2001 (Box R3779)
    - 2000 GI 072 - ASIA SOCIETY - PARTICIPATION AT SYMPOSIUM ON PEACE AND CIVIL SOCIETY IN AFGHANISTAN, 2000-2001 (Box R3779)
    - 2000 GI 073 - UNITED NATIONS DEVELOPMENT PROGRAMME - GLOBAL JUSTICE AND INCLUSION, 2000-2002 (Box R3779)
    - 2000 GI 074 - SYNERGOS INSTITUTE - GENERAL SUPPORT, 1999-2002 (Box R3779)
    - 2000 GI 076 - GLOBAL LABOUR INSTITUTE (SWITZERLAND) - INTERNATIONAL CONFERENCE OF FEMALE WORKERS, 2000-2002 (Box R3780)
    - 2000 GI 078 - STREETNET ASSOCIATION (SOUTH AFRICA) - WOMEN STREET VENDORS, 2000-2003 (Box R3780)
    - 2000 GI 079 - GEORGE MEANY CENTER FOR LABOR STUDIES - INTERNATIONAL CONFERENCE OF LABOR EDUCATORS, 2000-2005 (Box R3780)
    - 2000 GI 081 - UNIVERSITY OF MASSACHUSETTS (AMHERST) - RESTRUCTURING FINANCIAL SECTOR TO PROMOTE EGALITARIAN GROWTH, 2000-2001 (Box R3780)
    - 2000 GI 092 - WORLD BUSINESS COUNCIL FOR SUSTAINABLE DEVELOPMENT (SWITZERLAND) - MINING AND SUSTAINABLE DEVELOPMENT, 1999-2003 (Box R3780)
    - 2000 GI 094 - PROJECT UNDERGROUND - RESOURCE-BASED CONFLICTS WEBSITE, 2000-2001 (Box R3780)
    - 2000 GI 096 - LA TROBE UNIVERSITY (AUSTRALIA) - GLOBAL GOVERNANCE REFORM, 2000-2003 (Box R3780)
    - 2000 GI 098 - RICH, BRYAN - DOCUMETARY FILM, "BREAKING THE CODES", ON ETHIC CONFLICT IN BURUNDI, 1999-2001 (Box R3780)